/*
 * Script for index.html
 * requires scripts.js
 */

const doctorWho = {
  trivia: [
    {
      question:
        'When the Doctor meets Amelia Pond, what is it that he eats and actually likes?',
      answers: {
        2: 'Fish fingers and custard',
        1: 'An apple',
        3: 'A banana',
        4: 'Pie'
      },
      correctAnswer: '2'
    },
    {
      question:
        'Which one of the following is given the nickname "Potato Heads"?',
      answers: {
        1: 'Sontarans',
        2: 'Cyber men',
        3: 'Daleks',
        4: 'Ood'
      },
      correctAnswer: '1'
    },
    {
      question: 'What was Mickey called in the parallel universe?',
      answers: {
        4: 'Ricky ',
        2: 'Craig',
        3: 'Rory',
        1: 'Adam'
      },
      correctAnswer: '4'
    },
    {
      question:
        'In "The Christmas Invasion," The Doctor and Rose return to London. Who is the prime minister at the time?',
      answers: {
        1: 'Harriet Jones ',
        2: 'Winston Churchill',
        3: 'Craig Owens',
        4: 'Donna Noble'
      },
      correctAnswer: '1'
    },
    {
      question: 'Where did The Doctor and Rose first meet Captain Jack?',
      answers: {
        2: 'World War II',
        1: 'Gallifrey',
        3: 'Skaro',
        4: 'Mars'
      },
      correctAnswer: '2'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who was the 9th Doctor played by?',
      answers: {
        4: 'Christopher Eccleston ',
        2: 'David Tennant',
        3: 'Matt Smith',
        1: 'Paul McGann'
      },
      correctAnswer: '4'
    },
    {
      question:
        'Which one of the following villains is also a timelord like the Doctor?',
      answers: {
        4: 'The Master',
        2: 'Cyber Men',
        3: 'Ood',
        1: 'Abzorbalof'
      },
      correctAnswer: '4'
    },
    {
      question: 'Where is "Doctor Who" mainly filmed?',
      answers: {
        1: 'Cardiff, Wales',
        2: 'London, England',
        3: 'Edinburgh, Scotland',
        4: 'Cambridge, England'
      },
      correctAnswer: '1'
    },
    {
      question: 'What was the name of "the last human"?',
      answers: {
        2: 'Cassandra ',
        1: 'Rose',
        3: 'Jack',
        4: 'Sarah'
      },
      correctAnswer: '2'
    },
    {
      question:
        'Prime Minister of the United Kingdom during the 20th Century. This skilled veteran helped the Doctor defeat the Daleks, and even encountered the Silence in an altered timeline!',
      answers: {
        1: 'Neville Chamberlain',
        2: 'Clement Attlee',
        4: 'Harold Macmillan',
        3: 'Winston Churchill'
      },
      correctAnswer: '3'
    }
  ]
};
